radiantinsights.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Radiant Insights - One Place For All Market Research Needs

Privacy Policy

    Radiant Insights knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Research and Markets, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

    ## What personal information about customers does Radiant Insights gather?

    The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your delivery of business information. 

    ## Here are the types of information we gather:

    Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our products, and communicating with you.
    
    Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies", and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Research and Markets.
    
    Note: Your browsing and purchasing patterns for market research information may be commercially sensitive. We recognize this. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Radiant Insights if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
    
    E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Radiant Insights if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences.
    Information from Other Sources: We might receive information about you or your organisation from other sources and add it to our account information.

    ## What about Cookies?

    Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide additional features such personalized information, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
    The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Research and Markets’ coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

    ## How secure is information about me?

    We protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
